George and Ira Gershwin Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 1-63)
  - Music from Shows (Box 1-47)
    - Girl crazy [1930] (Box 8-9)
      - Opening, Act II, Alternate title for "Land of the gay caballero," Box-Folder 9/15-16
      - Sam and Delilah
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 7 p., No lyric (Box-folder 9/18)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Albert Sirmay; 1, 9 p. (Box-folder 9/19)
        - 2 copyist manuscript piano-vocal scores; 9 p. ea. (Box-folder 9/19)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [4] p. (Box-folder 9/19)
      - Selection
        - Copyist manuscript orchestral parts (4), For oboe, E-flat alto saxophone, 2nd violin, and viola; Orchestrated by F. Henri Klickmann (Box-folder 9/20)
      - Something peculiar, See "Something peculiar" from Piccadilly to Broadway, Box-Folder 28/31
      - That lonesome cowboy won't be lonesome now, Alternate title for "Dance alone with you," Box-Folder 6/10-11
      - Treat me rough
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 6 p., No lyric (Box-folder 9/21)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] p. (Box-folder 9/21)
      - We're bronco busters, Alternate title for "Bronco busters," Box-Folder 9/1
      - When it's cactus time in Arizona, Alternate title for "Cactus time in Arizona," Box-Folder 9/5
      - You can't unscramble scrambled eggs
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1, 3] p., No lyric (Box-folder 9/22)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [1, 2] p., No lyric (Box-folder 9/22)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p., No lyric (Box-folder 9/22)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 9/22)
      - Lists of songs, running order
        - IG holograph/typescript manuscript; [3] p., For Philadelphia tryout, for New York opening (Box-folder 9/23)
      - Piano parts
        - IG holograph cover only (Box-folder 9/24)
    - Girl crazy [1960 revival] (Box 9)
      - Dawn of a new day
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 9/25)
    - Give a girl a break [film, 1953 revival] (Box 9-10)
      - Ach, du lieber oom-pah-pah
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [20] p. (Box-folder 9/26)
      - Applause, applause
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [7] p. (Box-folder 9/27)
      - Dreamworld
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 9 p. (Box-folder 9/28)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [10] p. (Box-folder 9/28)
      - Give a girl a break
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 6 p. (Box-folder 10/1)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [12] p. (Box-folder 10/1)
      - In our united state
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 10/2)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [17] p. (Box-folder 10/2)
      - It happens ev'ry time
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [12] p. (Box-folder 10/3)
      - Nothing is impossible
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 9 p. (Box-folder 10/4)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [6] p. (Box-folder 10/4)
      - Whizzin’ thru space [unfinished]
        - IG holograph lyric sheet; [2] p. (Box-folder 10/5)
      - Woman, there is no living with you
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 10/6)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [5] p. (Box-folder 10/6)
      - Outline
        - Typescript; 8 p., IG holograph emendations (Box-folder 10/7)
        - IG holograph lyric sheets; [4] p. (Box-folder 10/7)
      - Unidentified notes
        - IG holograph manuscripts; [5] p. (Box-folder 10/8)
    - The Goldwyn follies [1938] (Box 10)
      - Exposition
        - Typescript ballet scenario (3 versions); 3,2,2 p. (Box-folder 10/9)
      - I love to rhyme
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal sketch; [4] p. (Box-folder 10/10)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [6] p. (Box-folder 10/11)
      - I was doing all right
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal sketch; 3 p., Refrain only (Box-folder 10/12)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 10/13)
      - I'm not complaining
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 10/14)
        - Photocopied copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 10/14)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 10/14)
      - Just another rhumba
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [5] p., No lyric (Box-folder 10/15)
        - IG holograph/typescript/carbon copy lyric sheets; [11] p. (Box-folder 10/16)
      - Love is here to stay
        - Photocopied sheet music (German) (Box-folder 10/17)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [7] p. (Box-folder 10/17)
      - Love walked in
        - Photocopied sheet music (German) (Box-folder 10/18)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 10/18)
      - Spring again
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 10/19)
      - Miscellaneous notes
        - IG holograph manuscript; [4] p. (Box-folder 10/20)
    - Good morning, Judge [1919] (Box 10)
      - I was so young (You were so beautiful)
        - Frank Saddler holograph manuscript full score; 16 p. (Box-folder 10/21)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p., Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 10/22)
        - Manuscript lyric sheet (Box-folder 10/22)
      - There's more to the kiss than the x-x-x
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., Partial vocal line, no lyric (Box-folder 10/23)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 10/24)
    - Greenwich Village follies [1924] (Box 10)
      - Hot hindoo
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 10/25)
    - Half past eight [1918] (Box 10)
      - Cupid
        - Copyist manuscript piano score; [3] p. (Box-folder 10/26)
        - Photocopied copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 6 p., No lyric (Box-folder 10/26)
      - Half past eight
        - Photocopied copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 7 p., No lyric (Box-folder 10/27)
      - Hong Kong
        - Photocopied copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 6 p., No lyric (Box-folder 10/28)
      - Little sunbeam
        - Photocopied copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p., No lyric (Box-folder 10/29)
      - Ten commandments of love
        - Maurice DePackh holograph manuscript full score; 21 p. (Box-folder 10/30)
      - There's magic in the air
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheet; [2] p. (Box-folder 10/31)
      - Running order
        - Typescript list with emendations; [1] p. (Box-folder 10/32)
    - Kiss me, stupid [1964] (Box 11)
      - All the livelong day (and the long, long night)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [2] p., No lyric (Box-folder 11/1)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 11/1)
        - 2 photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal scores; 4 p. ea., Refrain has no lyric; IG holograph emendations (Box-folder 11/1)
        - 3 photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal scores; 4 p. ea., IG holograph emendations (Box-folder 11/1)
        - Photocopied (ozalid) piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 11/1)
        - Manuscript piano sketch; [2] p., Refrain only (Box-folder 11/1)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets and notes; [54] p. (Box-folder 11/2)
        - IG typescript lyric sheets; [5] p., Revised 2nd refrain for Ella Fitzgerald; Laid in: IG typescript letter to Ella Fitzgerald, 1964 September 30 (Box-folder 11/3)
      - I'm a poached egg
        - Manuscript piano-vocal sketch in the hand of Kay Swift; [1] p. (Box-folder 11/4)
        - Manuscript piano score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1] p., Refrain only (Box-folder 11/4)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 11/4)
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p., IG holograph emendations (Box-folder 11/4)
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p., Refrain only (Box-folder 11/4)
        - 2 photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 11/4)
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 6 p., Laid in: Photocopied IG typescript notes; [1] p. (Box-folder 11/4)
        - Sheet music with IG corrections (Box-folder 11/4)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [54] p. (Box-folder 11/5)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [11] p., Revised 3rd refrain for Ella Fitzgerald; Laid in: IG signed typescript letter to Ella Fitzgerald, 1964 September 30 (Box-folder 11/6)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [16] p. (Box-folder OV-1/3)
      - Sophia
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 7 p. (Box-folder 11/7)
        - 8 photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal scores; 7 p. ea., Seven have IG holograph emendations (Box-folder 11/7)
        - 3 photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 6 p., Two have emendations (Box-folder 11/7)
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p., No lyric (Box-folder 11/7)
        - Manuscript piano fragments; [1] p., Laid in: IG holograph letter to “Doc”, undated; IG holograph letter, undated (Box-folder 11/7)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [30] p. (Box-folder 11/7)
    - La-la-Lucille! [1919] (Box 11)
      - Kitchenette
        - 2 Frank Saddler holograph manuscript full scores; 6, 7 p., One incomplete (Box-folder 11/9)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [4] p. (Box-folder 11/10)
      - Love of a wife
        - Frank Saddler holograph manuscript full score; 16 p., Laid in: IG typescript notes; [1] p. (Box-folder 11/11)
      - Money
        - Frank Saddler holograph manuscript full score; 16 p. (Box-folder 11/12)
    - Ladies first [1918] (Box 11)
      - The real American folk song
        - GG and Kay Swift holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [7] p., No lyric (Box-folder 11/13)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 7 p. (Box-folder 11/14)
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 7 p. (Box-folder 11/14)
        - IG holograph/typescript/photocopied lyric sheets; [4] p., Laid in: Envelope with IG holograph manuscript (Box-folder 11/14)
    - Lady, be good! [1924] (Box 11-13)
      - The bad, bad men
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., No lyric (Box-folder 11/15)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; 3 p. (Box-folder 11/16)
      - Buy a little button from me
        - Typescript lyric sheet; [2] p. (Box-folder 11/17)
      - Carnival
        - Charles Grant holograph manuscript full score; 17 p. (Box-folder 11/18)
      - End of a string
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 11/19)
      - Evening star
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., No lyric (Box-folder 12/1)
        - GG holograph manuscript harmony sketch; [1] p., Adjoined with: “Opening, Act I, scene III” (vocal sketch, [1] p.) (Box-folder 12/2)
        - Photocopied copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [5] p. (Box-folder 12/3)
        - Photocopied GG holograph manuscript lead sheet; [2] p. (Box-folder 12/3)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 12/3)
        - Photocopied IG holograph/typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 12/3)
      - Fascinating rhythm
        - GG holograph manuscript piano score; [1,1] p., Verse only (Box-folder 12/4)
        - GG holograph manuscript piano score; [2] p., Refrain only; Caption title: Syncopated city (Box-folder 12/5)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Albert Sirmay; 7 p. (Box-folder 12/6)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p., No lyric; Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 12/6)
        - Photocopied sheet music (French) (Box-folder 12/6)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 12/6)
      - Fascinating rhythm - Interlude
        - GG holograph manuscript piano score; [1] p., Adjoined with: “Finale” (piano-vocal score, no lyric, [1] p.) (Box-folder 12/7)
      - Fascinating rhythm [revised version, ca. 1940s]
        - Typescript lyric sheet, Refrain only (Box-folder 12/8)
      - Finale, See "Fascinating rhythm - Interlude," Box-Folder 12/7
      - Finale, Act I
        - Max Steiner holograph manuscript full score; 18 p., Incomplete (Box-folder 12/9)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 12/10)
      - Finale, Act II
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 12/11)
      - The half of it dearie, blues
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p., Emendations in the hand of Albert Sirmay; Unidentified sketch material on verso of p. [3] (Box-folder 12/12)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [9] p. (Box-folder 12/12)
      - The half of it dearie, blues. Patter
        - Typescript lyric sheets (Box-folder 12/13)
      - Hang on to me
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score with; [4] p., Emendations in the hands of IG Albert Sirmay (Box-folder 12/14)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; one with corrections; [2] p. (Box-folder 12/14)
      - I'd rather Charleston
        - Typescript lyric sheets [2] p., One has emendations (Box-folder 12/15)
      - Juanita
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 12/16)
      - Leave it to love
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p., No lyric; Unidentified sketch material on p. [4] (Box-folder 12/17)
      - Linger in the lobby
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal sketch; [8] p., No lyric (Box-folder 12/18)
        - Robert Russell Bennett holograph manuscript full score; 29 p., Incomplete, p. 1 missing (Box-folder 12/19)
        - Typescript lyric sheets with corrections; [2] p. (Box-folder 12/19)
      - Little jazz bird
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., No lyric (Box-folder 12/21)
        - Albert Sirmay holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 7 p., No lyric (Box-folder 12/22)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 12/22)
      - Little theatre
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 12/23)
      - The man I love, See also "The man I love" from Strike up the band, Box-Folder OV-1/9 and 37/12
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [2] p., Verse only, no lyric (Box-folder 12/24)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 8 p., GG holograph emendations; No lyric (Box-folder 12/25)
        - Albert Sirmay holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 7 p. (Box-folder 12/26)
        - Photocopied sheet music (French version) (Box-folder 12/26)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 12/26)
      - Oh, lady be good!
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., Verse has no lyric, refrain has partial lyric (Box-folder 12/27)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 12/28)
        - Photocopied sheet music (German) (Box-folder 12/28)
        - Photocopied sheet music [fake], In caption in the hand of IG: We never did find out who started this fakery (Box-folder 12/29)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [6] p. (Box-folder 12/28)
      - Oh, what a lovely party, British title for "A wonderful party," Box-Folder 13/14
      - Opening, Act I
        - William Daly holograph manuscript full score; 31 p., Incomplete, p. 12 missing; Found with: Tell me more (Box-folder 12/30)
      - Opening, Act I, scene III, See "Evening star," Box-Folder 12/1-3
      - Opening, Act II, Alternate title for "Linger in the lobby," Box-Folder 12/18-19; Alternate title during pre-Broadway tour for "Weatherman and rainy-afternoon girls," Box-Folder 13/8-10
      - Overture
        - Manuscript full score; 15 p. (Box-folder 12/31)
      - Scene II, Act I
        - Stephen O. Jones holograph manuscript full score; 14 p. (Box-folder 12/32)
      - Scene III, Act I
        - Paul Lannin holograph manuscript full score; 33 [i.e., 36] p. (Box-folder 13/1)
      - Seeing Dickie home
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 13/2)
      - Selection
        - Robert Russell Bennett holograph manuscript (with printed portions) piano score; 19 p. (Box-folder 13/3)
      - Singin' Pete
        - Manuscript piano sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 13/4)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 13/4)
      - Six little rainy-afternoon girls, Alternate title for "Weatherman and rainy-afternoon girls," Box-Folder 13/8-10
      - So am I
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., No lyric (Box-folder 13/5)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Albert Sirmay; 7 p. (Box-folder 13/6)
        - Typescript/photocopied lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 13/6)
      - Swiss miss
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 13/7)
      - Syncopated city, Alternate title for "Fascinating rhythm," Box-Folder 12/4-8
      - Weatherman and rainy-afternoon girls
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal sketch; 10 [i.e., 9] p., No lyric (Box-folder 13/8)
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 11 p., No lyric (Box-folder 13/9)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] p. (Box-folder 13/10)
      - We're here because
        - Paul Lannin holograph manuscript full score; 20 p. (Box-folder 13/11)
        - Paul Lannin holograph manuscript short score; [1, 2] p. (Box-folder 13/11)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 13/12)
      - Will you remember me
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., No lyric (Box-folder 13/13)
        - Typescript/photocopied lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 13/13)
      - A wonderful party
        - Typescript lyric sheets (Box-folder 13/14)
      - Unidentified waltz
        - Manuscript piano sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 13/15)
    - Lady in the dark [1941] (Box 13-14)
      - Bats about you
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheet, Laid in: IG typescript notes; [3] p. (Box-folder 13/16)
      - The boss is bringing home a bride
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [2] p., Part of the "Hollywood daydream" (Box-folder 13/17)
      - Circus dream
        - IG holograph/typescript libretto/lyric sheets (5 versions), v. A: (early draft); 9 [i.e., 15] p.; Includes revision of p. [1]; v. B: 11 p.; Laid in: IG holograph notes; [1] p.; IG refers to this as the 3rd draft; 1st draft was apparently Minstrel dream; v. C: (carbon copy of v. B) with holograph emendations; 11 p.; v. D: 14 p.; v. E: (copy of v. D with IG holograph note); 14 p.; v. F: 13 p.; Laid in: IG typescript notes; [1] p.; Incomplete late draft; [1] p. (Box-folder 13/18)
      - First dream sequence, Alternate title for the "Glamour dream," Box-Folder 13/19
      - Fourth dream sequence, Alternate title for the "Hollywood daydream"
      - Glamour dream
        - IG holograph/typescript libretto/lyric sheets; 8 [i.e., 9] p., Incomplete, p. 5 is missing (Box-folder 13/19)
      - Hollywood daydream [unfinished], Sequence dropped from the production
      - Hollywood party, Alternate title for "Party parlando," Box-Folder 13/25
      - Home in San Fernando valley
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [2] p., Part of the "Hollywood daydream" (Box-folder 13/20)
      - It's never too late to Mendelssohn
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [3] p., Laid in: IG holograph/typescript notes; [1] p.; Originally part of the "Wedding dream," Box-Folder 13/30-31 (Box-folder 13/21)
      - Minstrel dream
        - IG holograph/typescript libretto/lyric sheets; [6] p., Incomplete; Laid in: IG holograph/typescript notes; [2] p. (Box-folder 13/22)
      - The minstrel show, Alternate title for the "Minstrel dream," Box-Folder 13/22
      - My ship
        - IG holograph lyric sheet; [2] p. (Box-folder 13/23)
      - One life to live
        - IG holograph/typescript/photocopied lyric sheets; [9] p., Laid in: IG holograph/typescript notes; [2] p.; Part of the "Glamour dream," Box-Folder 13/19 (Box-folder 13/24)
      - Party parlando
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [2] p., Part of the "Hollywood daydream" (Box-folder 13/25)
      - The saga of Jenny
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [16] p., Laid in: IG holograph/typescript notes; [1] p.; Part of the "Circus dream," Box-Folder 13/18 (Box-folder 13/26)
      - Second dream sequence, Alternate title for the "Wedding dream," Box-Folder 13/30-31
      - Third dream sequence, Alternate title for the "Circus dream," Box-Folder 13/18
      - This is new
        - Typescript lyric sheet, Part of the "Wedding dream," Box-Folder 13/30-31 (Box-folder 13/27)
      - Tschaikowsky (and other Russians)
        - IG holograph/typescript scenario/lyric sheets; [4] p., Laid in: IG typescript notes; [2] p.; Part of the "Circus dream," Box-Folder 13/18 (Box-folder 13/28)
      - Unforgettable
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [5] p., Laid in: IG holograph/typescript notes; [2] p.; Originally part of the "Wedding dream," Box-Folder 13/30-31 (Box-folder 13/29)
      - Wedding dream
        - IG holograph/typescript libretto/lyric sheets; [11] p., In headings: Bolero; Laid in: IG holograph/typescript notes; [12] p. (Box-folder 13/30)
        - Typescript libretto/lyric sheets (4 versions), v. A: 10 p. (final draft); v. B: 8 p. (earlier draft); v. C: 8 p. (carbon copy of v. B); v. D: 8 p. (carbon copy of v. B); Incomplete earlier draft; [2] p.; Laid in: IG holograph/typescript notes; [2] p. (Box-folder 13/31)
      - Dream sequence scenarios, See also the "Wedding dream," Box-Folder 13/30-31; the "Circus dream," Box-Folder 13/18; and the "Hollywood daydream"
        - Moss Hart typescript scenarios; [3] p., Scenarios for the "Wedding dream," Box-Folder 13/30-31 and the "Circus dream," Box-Folder 13/18; Laid in: IG holograph/typescript notes; [2] p. (Box-folder 13/32)
      - Lyric book
        - Typescript; [36] p., Laid in: IG holograph/typescript notes; [2] p. (Box-folder 14/1)
      - Script
        - Typescript; [85] p., Titled: I am listening (Box-folder 14/2)
    - Let 'em eat cake (1933) (Box 14-15)
      - All the mothers of the nation
        - GG holograph manuscript lead sheet sketch; [1] p., Caption title: Air for Mary (Box-folder 14/3)
      - Blue, blue, blue
        - GG holograph manuscript melody sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 14/4)
      - Climb up the social ladder
        - GG holograph manuscript melody sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 14/5)
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [7] p., Unidentified sketch material on p. [7] (Box-folder 14/6)
      - Cloistered from the noisy city, Alternate title for "The Union League," Box-Folder 15/2
      - Comes the revolution
        - Photocopied manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [2] p. (Box-folder 14/7)
      - Finale, Act I
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 29 p., Partial lyric (Box-folder 14/8)
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal sketches; 13 [i.e., 10] p. (Box-folder 14/9)
        - GG holograph manuscript outline of musical selections with drawings; [1] p. (Box-folder 14/10)
      - Hanging Throttlebottom in the morning
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [7] p., Ensemble section has no lyric (Box-folder 14/11)
        - GG holograph manuscript lead sheet; [1] p., Partial lyric (Box-folder 14/12)
      - It isn't what you did
        - GG holograph manuscript lead sheet; [1] p., Lyric fragment (Box-folder 14/13)
      - League of Nations finale
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 16 p. (Box-folder 14/14)
        - Holograph manuscript lead sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 14/15)
      - Let 'em eat cake
        - Holograph manuscript lead sheet; 1 p. (Box-folder 14/16)
      - Limerick
        - GG holograph manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 14/17)